{
    "channels": [
        "bot_testing",
        "trusted_house",
        "voice-text-chat",
        "members-voice-text-chat",
        "use-bots-here"
    ],
    "commands": [
        "start",
        "end",
        "add",
        "cats",
        "help"
    ],
    "categories": [
        "Any",
        "Video-Games",
        "Movies",
        "Nature",
        "Maths",
        "Computer-Science",
        "Geography"
    ],
    "questions": [
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What was Mario from Super Mario Bros. original name?",
            "answer": "Jumpman",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What was the forest area from Super Mario World called?",
            "answer": "Forest of Illusion",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What was the second Ratchet and Clank game called in the UK? [Hint: Ratchet and Clank: <???>]",
            "answer": "Locked and Loaded",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is 2 + 2?",
            "answer": "4",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What's the derivate of e?",
            "answer": "e"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What is the capital city of England?",
            "answer": "London",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What USA state will you find the city of Orlando?",
            "answer": "Florida",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What type is the pok√©mon bidoof?",
            "answer": "Normal",
            "author": "202103129330810880"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What type of Pokemon is Weedle?",
            "answer": "bug",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What was the city of Istanbul called before 1930?",
            "answer": "Constantinople",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What is the capital city of France?",
            "answer": "Paris",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Computer-Science",
            "question": "Who was the original creator of C++?",
            "answer": "Bjarne Stroustrup",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "Who was the director of the 1997 film 'Titanic'?",
            "answer": "James Cameron",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What is the most famous game by Bay12Games?",
            "answer": "Dwarf Fortress",
            "author": "202103129330810880"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Nature",
            "question": "What is a group of lions called? [1 word]",
            "answer": "Pride",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "Who was the lead game designer of Skyrim?",
            "answer": "Todd Howard",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "What was the first Star Wars movie released? Hint: Star Wars: <your answer here>",
            "answer": "A New Hope",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Computer-Science",
            "question": "What language is C++ a superset of?",
            "answer": "C",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "Which country lies on the border between Spain and France?",
            "answer": "Andorra",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Computer-Science",
            "question": "What does USB stand for?",
            "answer": "Universal Serial Bus",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is square root of -1?",
            "answer": "i"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Nature",
            "question": "How many legs do all insects have?",
            "answer": "6",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Nature",
            "question": "What is the only type of bird which has the ability to fly backwards?",
            "answer": "hummingbird",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Nature",
            "question": "What shape is a goats pupil?",
            "answer": "rectangle",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Movies",
            "question": "How many stars are on the Paramount studio logo?",
            "answer": "22",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Geography",
            "question": "What is the capital city of Japan?",
            "answer": "Tokyo",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "In Minecraft, what is the surface block of the Mushroom biome?",
            "answer": "Mycelium",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is the seventh number of the Fibbonacci sequence?",
            "answer": "13",
            "author": "231104432102834176"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Video-Games",
            "question": "What is the tallest mountain in Skyrim? [4 words]",
            "answer": "Throat of the World",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Computer-Science",
            "question": "A NOR gate is considered a universal gates; What is the other universal gate?",
            "answer": "NAND",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        },
        {
            "cat": "Maths",
            "question": "What is 9 squared?",
            "answer": "81",
            "author": "115025985405059076"
        }
    ]
}